http://www.camodels.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Product Design
In compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), CA Models Limited has revised its Privacy and Cookies Policy.At CA Models, we are dedicated to gaining and maintaining your trust as a valued visitor to our website, or as a subscriber to our newsletter.On this page, you’ll find information on what we do with the data we collect when you visit our website, or when you subscribe to our email newsletter.
VISITORS TO OUR WEBSITE
When you visit our website (https://www.camodels.co.uk), we collect standard visitor information via a third-party application called Google Analytics.This allows us to gauge visitor numbers and observe visitor behaviour patterns. It does not, however, allow us to identify individual visitors. The information we collect via Google Analytics is completely anonymous and is used only to improve our website’s performance and your user experience.If we do wish to collect any personally identifiable information, we will do so in a transparent manner.
NEWSLETTER SIGN UP
As part of the subscription process for our newsletter, you will be asked for your email address.We will only use your email address to keep you up-to-date with the latest news from CA Models. We do not share email lists with other businesses or organisations, nor will we sell your data to a third party.CA Models currently uses MailChimp to deliver our newsletters. This allows us to gather information regarding email opens and clicks, which in turn helps us measure and improve our email newsletter. Your information is held securely on MailChimp’s servers. If you’d like more information about MailChimp’s own privacy policy, click here.If you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter, you can do so at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.
ENQUIRIES (CONTACT FORM COMPLETION)
When you complete our enquiry form, you will be asked for three pieces of mandatory information: your full name; your email address; and your message. Additionally, you may choose to include your company name.We use this information to deal with your requests and enquiries, and to put you in touch with the sales person at CA Models to help answer your questions.We do not sell any of the information collected through the CA Models website, or use your personal information for any other purposes than those outlined above.
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
In accordance with GDPR, you have the right to access, review, and erase any of your personal information currently held by CA Models. Please email your request to info@camodels.co.uk.
SECURITY CERTIFICATES
When you share your personal information with us, we take the necessary steps to ensure it is delivered and held securely. Any sensitive information is encrypted and protected when sent, and our security certificates are routinely monitored and renewed prior to expiration to maintain validity.
COOKIES POLICY
Cookies are text files containing small amounts of data which are sent to your browser when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the website on each subsequent visit, or to a different website that recognises the cookie.We use cookies to better understand how frequently certain pages are visited, and to make our website more user-friendly.Below you’ll find a list of the different types of cookies we use on the CA Models website.
By using the CA Models website, you agree that we can place the following cookies on your device.
These cookies collect anonymous information about how visitors use the website – for example, which pages are visited most often, and the types of actions visitors take when they reach particular pages.These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. We use these cookies only to understand visitor behaviour, and to improve our website’s performance.
Third Party Cookies
These cookies allow third parties to track how you use their applications.For example, you may wish to share one of our tweets via Facebook or Twitter doing so, you may be sent cookies from those websites. We do not control these cookies, so please check with the respective websites should you have any questions regarding how they work and how to manage them.
HOW LONG ARE COOKIES STORED FOR?
Session cookies allow webmasters to link the actions of a user during a specific browser session. A browser session begins when a user opens the browser window, and it ends when they close the browser window. Session cookies are temporary, and once the browser session ends, all session cookies are deleted.On the other hand, persistent cookies remain on a user’s device for a period of time specified by the cookie. These cookies are activated every time a user visits the website that generated the cookie in question.If you’d like to learn more about how cookies work, how to reject them, and how to delete them, we recommend reading:www.allaboutcookies.orgwww.youronlinechoices.eu
CA Models
Borrowmeadow Road, Springkerse Industrial Estate, Stirling, Scotland, FK7 7UW
Sitemap
Privacy Policy
Our website uses cookies to help improve the site and provide you with a better user experience.
To continue using the site, please consent by clicking on the button below.
Yes, I accept.
